{
    "id": "a352adbb148f45cca278b19aa915a38e",
    "title": "Adjective Or Present Participle",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Interesting though it was, we didnâ€™t enjoy the concert much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Interesting is an adjective",
                "Interesting is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "901e61b0afe7490d89742a7a74d76872"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was raining when I got home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Raining is an adjective",
                "Raining is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0b519ebc9de440c922fcbea4b6aa6a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I love the noise of falling rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Falling is an adjective",
                "Falling is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f66f542e8aef4b03ba38c8d0524ab898"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is a pressing problem.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Pressing is an adjective",
                "Pressing is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8489843dbd834935a1a1859c34967e33"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was writing a letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Writing is an adjective",
                "Writing is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94612ee9933b48dc8e1beacd7593fbce"
        },
        {
            "question": "The lecture was very interesting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Interesting is an adjective",
                "Interesting is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8fd494a7e94a452b880051510dcc786e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is an interesting writer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Interesting is an adjective",
                "Interesting is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5650a9dff5c47f3bbfd89ae4f2adc64"
        },
        {
            "question": "The woodcutter was felling trees.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Felling is an adjective",
                "Felling is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8850cc75c4ff461a978792387cf0f6ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news was exciting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Exciting is an adjective",
                "Exciting is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ccf0c27e1f0d42c2b1b46ffbbc4a5647"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was working on that report when she called.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Working is an adjective",
                "Working is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e67aea06bab5444c856c55e96b034a4b"
        }
    ]
}